(Amy:)What's the problem?
(Bernadette:)They're just asking me
(Bernadette:)all sorts of questions
I can't answer.
(Amy:)Just change the subject.
(Bernadette:)I suppose I could get them back
to talking about Leonard
(Bernadette:)going to India
to meet Priya's parents.
What?!
(Bernadette:)They said something about
going there this summer.
(Penny:)What, are they getting engaged?
(Bernadette:)I don't know. I was too busy
covering my heinie
(Bernadette:)on Amy's stupid
astronaut story!
(Amy:)What astronaut story?
(Bernadette:)You texted me Penny's
dating an astronaut.
I texted "architect."
That's amusing.
(Amy:)Auto-correct
must've changed it.
(Bernadette:)Yeah, it's hysterical.
(Penny:)All right, look, just forget
about the astronaut.
(Amy:)Architect. Where would you
have met an astronaut?
(Penny:)Look, just find out what's up
with this trip to India.
(Bernadette:)I don't want
to do this anymore!
(Penny:)Don't you quit on us!
(Howard(knocking on bathroom door):)Bernie, you okay?
(Bernadette(screaming):)It was an architect!
(Raj:)Thank you for coming
with me, Sheldon.
(Raj:)You're a good friend.